Guide to the Charles E. Palm papers,1956-1986.
Palm, Charles E. papers,1956-1986.
  - Cornell University Center for International Studies. Mellor, John W.; Cornell University, Center for International Studies., 1961-1962 (Box 10, Folder 70)
  - Library, University. McCarthy, Stephen A., 1961-1962 (Box 10, Folder 71)
  - New York State College of Agriculture, Livestock Advisory Council., 1961-1962 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Los Banos, 1960, 1961, 1962. Umali, D.L.; Mellor, John W.; Ford Foundation; Rockefeller Foundation; Univ. of the Philippines; United States, Agency for International Development; New York State College of Agriculture, Los Banos Project. (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - W.I. Myers. Myers, William I.; Carson, Rachel; Univ. of Liberia; Chemical sprays., 1961-1962 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - NSF Undergraduate Teaching Proposal. Hastie, John W.; National Science Foundation., 1961-1962 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Graduate School of Nutrition. Barnes, Richard H.; Cornell University, Graduate School of Nutrition., 1961-1962 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Open House, College of Agriculture., 1961-1962 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Orientation of Foreign Graduate Schools Committee. Hearne, Cannon C.; Fosbrink, Raleigh H.; Kennedy, W. Keith; Boynton, Damon; United States, Agency for International Development; Rockefeller Foundation; Ford Foundation., 1961-1962 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Outlook Conference., 1961-1962 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Cornell Plantations. Seeley, John G.; Rockwell, George H.; O'Connor, Audrey H.; Cornell Plantations., 1961-1962 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Cornell Plantations Committee. Swanson, Gustav A.; Rockwell, George H.; MacDaniels, Laurence H.; Seeley, John G.; Wright, T.P.; Buck, Harry E.; Banks, Harlan P.; Cornell Plantations., 1960-1962 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - College Poultry Committee., 1961-1962 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Poultry, Test Farms. Gridley, John C., 1961-1962 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Profile of Class Entering 1961., 1961-1962 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Committee on Public Relations for Agriculture. Durfee, Arthur E., 1961-1962 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Publications Committee. Russell, Charles C., 1961-1962 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Radiation Safety Committee., 1961-1962 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Rent-A-Car Information for College Personnel., 1961-1962 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Safety Division., 1961 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Seed Committee, College of Agriculture. Anderson, Ronald E., 1961-1962 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Service Emblem Awards. Willers, Diedrich K., 1961 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Soil Science Institute., 1961 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Southeast Asia Project Proposal 1962, Possible Renewal of Los Banos Project. United States Agency for International Development; New York State College of Agriculture, Los Banos Project., 1961-1962 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Student Exchange Program for Argentina., 1961-1962 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Summer Session and Extramural Courses. Watkins, Thomas C.; Smith, William A., 1961-1962 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Transfers from Agricultural Technical Institutes and Community Colleges., 1961-1962 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Travel Policies., 1962 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - TV Film Center. Canoyer, Helen G.; Phillips, Elmer S., 1961-1962 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Veterinary College. Poppensiek, George C.; Comar, Cyril L.; New York State Veterinary College., 1961-1962 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Veterinary College Council. New York State Veterinary College, Council., 1961-1962 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Water Resources. New York State College of Agriculture, Water Resources Center., 1959-1962 (Box 11, Folder 30-31)
  - Weed Control Research Program., 1962 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Morton Adams. Adams, Morton; Severinghaus, Leslie R.; New York State Agricultural Businessmen's Council., 1961-1962 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Agricultural Research Benefits Consumers. Freeman, Orville L.; "Agricultural Research Benefits Consumers" (publication)., 1961-1962 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Agricultural Research Institute., 1961-1962 (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Agricultural Science Youth Program., 1961-1962 (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Agricultural and Technical Institutes. Laffin, Charles W., 1962 (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Allegany County. Peterson, Arthur H., 1961 (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Alpha Zeta. Rockefeller, Nelson A.; Middaugh, Wesley S.; Alpha Zeta., 1961-1962 (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - American Agriculturist. Ingalls, Irving W.; American Agriculturist Foundation., 1961-1962 (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - Area Redevelopment Program., 1961-1962 (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - Arkansas Alumni Association. Univ. of Arkansas., 1961-1962 (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - B Miscellaneous. Berg, Sherwood O.; Beneway, Frank W., 1961-1962 (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - Bankers School of Agriculture., 1961-1962 (Box 11, Folder 44)
  - Charles Dana Bennett. Bennett, Charles Dana; Foundation for American Agriculture; Farm Film Foundation; "The Unseen Harvesters" (film)., 1961 (Box 11, Folder 45)
  - Blair, Howard E., 1961-1962 (Box 11, Folder 46)
  - C Miscellaneous. Comar, Cyril L.; Campbell, Howard H.; Teachers for East Africa., 1961-1962 (Box 11, Folder 47)
  - "Careers in World Agriculture" (Publication)., 1961-1962 (Box 11, Folder 48)
  - Carey, Daniel J., 1961-1962 (Box 11, Folder 49)
  - United States Chamber of Commerce, Agricultural Committee. Garver, Walter B., 1961-1962 (Box 11, Folder 50)
  - Christmas Tree Growers. Clark, Bion J.; New York Christmas Tree Growers Association., 1961-1962 (Box 11, Folder 51)
  - Citizens Advisory Committee. United States Food and Drug Administration, Citizens Advisory Committee., 1961-1962 (Box 11, Folder 52)
  - Cohn Farm, Operation Statement for Calendar Year 1961. Cohn, Herman M.; Cohn Farm., 1961-1962 (Box 11, Folder 53)
  - D Miscellaneous. Donlon, Mary H., 1961-1962 (Box 11, Folder 54)
  - Dairy Herd Improvement Association. Dairy industry., 1961-1962 (Box 11, Folder 55)
  - Dairy Products Improvement Institute. Dahlberg, Arthur C., 1961-1962 (Box 11, Folder 56)
  - Dairymen's League Cooperative Association., 1961-1962 (Box 11, Folder 57)
  - E Miscellaneous. Elliott, Lloyd H., 1961-1962 (Box 11, Folder 58)
  - Eastman Stage. Hopper, Nelson F., 1961-1962 (Box 11, Folder 59)
  - Empire Livestock Marketing Cooperative., 1961 (Box 11, Folder 60)
  - Empire State Farm Show, Inc., 1961-1962 (Box 11, Folder 61)
  - Empire State Potato Club. Evans, H.J.; Potato industry., 1961-1962 (Box 11, Folder 62)
  - Empire State Soil Fertility Association., 1961-1962 (Box 11, Folder 63)
  - Entomological Society of America. Wolfenberger, D.O., 1961-1962 (Box 11, Folder 64)
  - F Miscellaneous. Foster, Edward S.; Freeman, Orville L.; Anthology of American Agricultural Writing; Farm Journal., 1961-1962 (Box 11, Folder 65)
  - History, Farm Bureau Associations. Simons, Lloyd R., 1961-1962 (Box 11, Folder 66)
  - Farm-City Week Program., 1961-1962 (Box 11, Folder 67)
  - Farm Credit Banks of Springfield., 1961-1962 (Box 11, Folder 68)
  - Empire State Farm Show, Inc., 1961-1962 (Box 11, Folder 69)
  - Federal Land Bank. Hughes, Howell., 1961 (Box 11, Folder 70)
  - Feed Grain Program., 1961-1962 (Box 11, Folder 71)
  - Fish and Wildlife Management, Planning Committee. New York State Fish and Wildlife Management Board., 1961-1962 (Box 11, Folder 72)
  - Food and Drug Administration. United States Food and Drug Administration., 1961-1962 (Box 11, Folder 73)
  - Food Processing Extension Project. New York State Cooperative Extension Service., 1961-1962 (Box 11, Folder 74)
  - Foreign Agriculture. Peterson, Maurice L., 1961 (Box 11, Folder 75)
  - Forest Landowners Forum. Hamilton, Lawrence S., 1961-1962 (Box 11, Folder 76)
  - Conservation Problems and Research Conference, Forestry., 1961-1962 (Box 11, Folder 77)
  - Forestry. Shirley, Hardy L.; New York State College of Forestry., 1961-1962 (Box 11, Folder 78)
  - Frozen Food Conference, 9-10 APR 1962., 1961-1962 (Box 11, Folder 79)
  - G Miscellaneous. Gore, K.S.; Gysin, Hans., 1961-1962 (Box 11, Folder 80)
  - Gamma Sigma Delta., 1961-1962 (Box 11, Folder 81)
  - General Foods Scholarships. General Foods Corporation., 1961-1962 (Box 11, Folder 82)
  - Grange League Federation. Milliman, Thomas E.; Fallon, Edmund H.; Taber, Paul; Goldwater, Barry; Ranney, Warren A.; Potato industry., 1961-1962 (Box 11, Folder 83)
  - Grange League Federation, Plant Breeding Research Grants., 1961-1962 (Box 11, Folder 84)
  - Grange League Federation, Seminars. Tarbell, Seeber C., 1961-1962 (Box 11, Folder 85)
  - Gold Seal Vineyards. Frank, Konstantin; Barton, Donald W.; Fournier, Charles; Wine industry; Vinifera., 1961-1962 (Box 11, Folder 86)
  - Gypsy Moth. Alampi, Phillip; Gypsy moth., 1961-1962 (Box 11, Folder 87)
  - H Miscellaneous. Hobson, Jesse E.; Helmerking, Wilhelm., 1961-1962 (Box 11, Folder 88)
  - High School Natural Science Program. Hogue, Douglas E., 1961-1962 (Box 11, Folder 89)
  - I Miscellaneous. International Rice Research Institute., 1961-1962 (Box 11, Folder 90)
  - Instituto Colombiano Agropecuario Para La Educacion La Extension Y La Investigacion. Instituto Colombiano Agropecuario., 1961-1962 (Box 11, Folder 91)
  - International Agricultural Development. Rovetch, Warren; Education Research Associates., 1961-1962 (Box 11, Folder 92)
  - International Agricultural Development. Mellor, John W., 1961 (Box 11, Folder 93)
  - International Cooperation Administration. Beery, Lawrence A., 1961 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Interstate Commission on Lake Champlain Basin. Miller, Paul R., 1961-1962 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - J Miscellaneous. Johannessen, George A., 1961-1962 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - K Miscellaneous. Kelly, John W., 1961-1962 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - L Miscellaneous. Logothetis, Clerhos., 1961-1962 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - American Assn. of Land Grant Colleges and State Universities. Kennedy, W. Keith., 1961-1962 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Water Resources Committee of the American Assn. of Land Grant Colleges and State Universities., 1961-1962 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - American Assn. of Land Grant Colleges and State Universities, Future of Agriculture Division Committee. Kottman, Roy M., 1961-1962 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Land Grant Background. Russell, Dean W., 1961-1962 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Donald Lerch and Company. Lerch, Donald; National Agricultural Chemicals Association., 1961-1962 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - M Miscellaneous. Mackesey, Thomas W.; Merrill, Leland G.; McClellan, Robert; McManus, John F.; Rockefeller Foundation; McGraw-Hill Book Company., 1961-1962 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Metropolitan Cooperative Milk Producers' Bargaining Agency., 1961-1962 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Michigan Farm Economics. Hathaway, Dale E., 1961-1962 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - N Miscellaneous. New York Florists' Club; New York State Grape Growers Cooperative., 1961-1962 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - National Academy of Sciences, Agricultural Board. Campbell, Frank L., 1962 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - National Agricultural Chemicals Association. Hayley, Denis., 1961-1962 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Summary of Progress of the National Agricultural Extension Center for Advanced Study., 1961-1962 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - National Association of County Agricultural Agents. Campbell, Howard H., 1961-1962 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Committee on National Medal of Science. National Science Foundation., 1961-1962 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - National Potato Council., 1962 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Cooperative Program, State Units, Natural Resources. Wickham, Donald J.; Fenton, William N.; Shirley, Hardy L.; New York State Dept, of Agriculture and Markets., 1961-1962 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - New York State Agricultural Society. Milliman, Thomas E., 1961-1962 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - New York Artificial Breeders' Cooperative. Earl, J. Stanley; Krumm, Charles J., 1961-1962 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - New York State Canners and Freezers Association. Regan, Michael E., 1961-1962 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - New York State Canners and Freezers Association, Annual Meeting. Tyler, W.D., 1961-1962 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - New York State Concord Grape Production Research Fund., 1961-1962 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - New York State Conference Board of Farm Organizations., 1961-1962 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - New York Farm Bureau. Foster, Edward S., 1961-1962 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Farm Organization Conference., 1961-1962 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - New York State Grange., 1961-1962 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - New York State Horticultural Society. LaMont, Thomas E., 1961-1962 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - New York State Nurserymen's Association Meeting. Kirk, Edwin W.; Regulatory control., 1961-1962 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - New York State Seed Association. Gardner, George G.; Sherman, Richard; New York Foundation of Seed Stocks Cooperative; New York Certified Seed Growers Cooperative., 1961-1962 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - New York Certified Seed Growers Cooperative. Sherman, Richard., 1961-1962 (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Northeast Dairy Housing Workshop., 1961-1962 (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Northeastern Agricultural Experiment Stations. Personius, Catherine J.; Horsfall, James G., 1961-1962 (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - Northeastern Weed Control Conference. Southwick, Lawrence., 1961-1962 (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - State Advisory Council Report. New York State Dept, of Labor., 1961-1962 (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - New York State Dept, of Agriculture and Markets. Wickham, Donald J.; Dalrymple, Daniel M.; Kilgallen, Joseph W.; Anderson, Ronald E.; Pine Tree Dry Bean Growers Association; Residues., 1961-1962 (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - New York State Assembly. Curto, Ernest., 1961-1962 (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - New York State Budget Office. Hurd, T. Norman; Peterson, Arthur H., 1961-1962 (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - New York State Dept, of Commerce. McHugh, Keith S., 1961-1962 (Box 12, Folder 42)
  - New York State Conservation Dept. Heacox, Cecil E.; Wilm, Harold G., 1961-1962 (Box 12, Folder 43)
  - New York State Conservation Advisory Committee. Downey, Charles G.; Wilm, Harold G.; New York State Conservation Dept., Soil Conservation Committee., 1961-1962 (Box 12, Folder 44)
  - New York State Education Dept. Fretwell, Elbert K., 1961-1962 (Box 12, Folder 45)
  - New York State Fish and Wildlife Management Board. Cheatum, E.L., 1961-1962 (Box 12, Folder 46)
  - New York State Forest Practice Board., 1962 (Box 12, Folder 47)
  - New York State Government Bills. MacCrate, Robert; Seeley, John G., 1961-1962 (Box 12, Folder 48)
  - Governor's Office. MacCrate, Robert; Rockefeller, Nelson A., 1961-1962 (Box 12, Folder 49)
  - New York State Office for Regional Development., 1961 (Box 12, Folder 50)
  - New York State Senate. Gordon, Janet Hill., 1961-1962 (Box 12, Folder 51)
  - Small Fruit Commodity Committee. Fruit industry., 1961-1962 (Box 12, Folder 52)
  - New York State Soil Conservation Committee. Downey, Charles G.; Kerr, Harry A.; New York State Conservation Dept., Soil Conservation Committee., 1960-1962 (Box 12, Folder 53)
  - New York State Conservation Dept., Soil Conservation Committee. Kerr, Harry A.; McClellan, Robert., 1960-1962 (Box 12, Folder 54)
  - 0 Miscellaneous. Osorio, Jose M., 1961-1962 (Box 12, Folder 55)
  - P Miscellaneous. Prosser, Arthur E.; Pack, A. Boyd; Pfizer and Company., 1961-1962 (Box 12, Folder 56)
  - Phi Beta Kappa., 1961 (Box 12, Folder 57)
  - Programs, Other. New York State Arborists Association., 1961-1962 (Box 12, Folder 58)
  - R Miscellaneous. Rockefeller, Nelson A.; Rockwell, George H.; Ryan, John F.; Roth, Roger W., 1961-1962 (Box 12, Folder 59)
  - Reciprocal Meat Conference. Kunkle, Lawrence E., 1961 (Box 12, Folder 60)
  - Refrigerator Warehouses, Inc. New York State Association of Refrigerated Warehouses., 1961-1962 (Box 12, Folder 61)
  - Rice Debate., 1961-1962 (Box 12, Folder 62)
  - Rockefeller Foundation. Moseman, A.H.; McKelvey, John J.; Wernimont, Kenneth; Rockefeller Foundation., 1961-1962 (Box 12, Folder 63)
  - Rockefeller Foundation Grant for Plant Physiology. Rockefeller Foundation., 1961-1962 (Box 12, Folder 64)
  - S Miscellaneous. Sadd, C.W.; Shell Chemical Company., 1961-1962 (Box 12, Folder 65)
  - Salaries for Selected Land Grant Colleges., 1961-1962 (Box 12, Folder 66)
  - SPICE, New York State Poultry Industry Cooperative Effort. Prosser, Arthur E.; Webster, Ralph H.; Grange League Federation; New York State Poultry Coordinated Effort; Poultry industry., 1961-1962 (Box 12, Folder 67)
  - SPISE, Special Products in Special Education, Undergraduate Research Participation. New York State College of Agriculture, Dept, of Plant Pathology., 1961-1962 (Box 12, Folder 68)
  - Starling Control. Ryan, John F.; Eadie, W. Robert., 1961-1962 (Box 12, Folder 69)
  - State Fair., 1961-1962 (Box 12, Folder 70)
  - SUNY, Thomas H. Hamilton, President. Hamilton, Thomas H.; SUNY., 1961-1962 (Box 12, Folder 71)
  - SUNY, Charles H. Foster, Controller. Foster, Charles H.; SUNY., 1961-1962 (Box 12, Folder 72)
  - SUNY, International Committee on Foreign Proj ects. Goodman, Zmira., 1961-1962 (Box 12, Folder 73)
  - SUNY, Minutes, Board of Trustees. SUNY, Board of Trustees., 1961-1962 (Box 12, Folder 74-75)
  - SUNY, Minutes, Faculty Senate. SUNY, Faculty Senate., 1961-1962 (Box 12, Folder 76)
  - SUNY, Miscellaneous. Orvis, Paul B.; Hamilton, Thomas H.; SUNY, Research Office., 1961-1962 (Box 12, Folder 77)
  - SUNY, Public Education., 1961-1962 (Box 12, Folder 78)
  - SUNY, Regents Proposal for Expansion and Improvement of Education. Kille, Frank R.; SUNY., 1961 (Box 12, Folder 79)
  - SUNY, Salary Study., 1961-1962 (Box 12, Folder 80)
  - SUNY, Unit Heads Meeting., 1961-62 (Box 12, Folder 81)
  - T Miscellaneous. Todd, Walter L.; Taylor Wine Company., 1961-1962 (Box 12, Folder 82)
  - U Miscellaneous. United Nations, UNESCO; United Fruit Company; Union Carbide Company., 1961-1962 (Box 12, Folder 83)
  - Universities and Cc-leges. Pennsylvania State Univ., 1961-1962 (Box 12, Folder 84)
  - United States Dept, of Agriculture, Miscellaneous. Hearne, Cannon C.; Freeman, Orville L.; United States Dept, of Agriculture, Agricultural Research Service; United States Dept, of Agriculture, Foreign Agricultural Service., 1961-1962 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - United States Dept, of Agriculture, Rural Development Program Committee., 1961-1962 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - United States Dept, of Agriculture, Soil Conservation Service. Cohn, Morris M.; Stafford, Irving B., 1961-1962 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - V Miscellaneous. Vlitos, A.J., 1961-1962 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Vegetable, Potato, Fruit Growers Associations Meeting. Wickham, Donald J.; New York State Vegetable Growers Association; New York State Potato Growers Cooperative; New York State Horticultural Society., 1961-1962 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - W Miscellaneous. Willers, Diedrich K.; Webb, Rufus; Wickham, John; Whetzel, Amy; Koinonia Foundation., 1961-1962 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Weather Bureau. Pack, A. Boyd., 1961-1962 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Winemakers Conference, 11 DEC 1961. Fournier, Charles; Wine industry; Vinifera., 1961-1962 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Wine Industries. Wine industry; Vinifera., 1961-1962 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - President's Office. Malott, Deane W.; Dean, Arthur H.; Univ. of the Philippines; New York State College of Agriculture, Agronomy building., 1962-1963 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - President's Report. Malott, Deane W., 1962-1963 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - President D.W. Malott Luncheon. Malott, Deane W., 1962-1963 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Dean, Personal. Dean, Arthur H., 1963 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Dean's List., 1962-1963 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Dean Palm's Advisory Committee for Headship in Botany. Srb, Adrian M.; Banks, Harlan P.; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept, of Botany., 1962-1963 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Undergraduate Deans Meeting., 1962 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Vice-President in Charge of Development. Zwingle, J.L.; Bruska, Walter G., 1962-1963 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Vice-President of Research. Wright, T.P.; Hastie, John W., 1962-1963 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Vice-President for Student Affairs. Summerskill, John; Taietz, Philip., 1962-1963 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Controller A.H. Peterson. Peterson, Arthur H.; Kennedy, W. Keith., 1962-1963 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Director of Admissions. Storandt, Robert W.; Snickenberger, Walter A.; Cornell University, Office of Admissions., 1962-1963 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Ag Domecon Council. Dondero, Timothy J.; New York State College of Agriculture, Ag-Domecon., 1962-1963 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Agricultural Economics. Hedlund, Glenn W.; How, R. Brian; Cunningham, Lowell C.; Derr, Deri; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept, of Agricultural Economics., 1962-1963 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Agricultural Engineering, Esada Program. New York State College of Agriculture, Dept, of Agricultural Engineering; New York State College of Agriculture, Esada Program; Atomic power., 1963 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Agricultural Leaders Forum, 1963. Kennedy, W. Keith. (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - College, Agriculture and Markets, Dairy Marketing., 1962-1963 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Agronomy Building, State University. Fitzgerald, John; New York State College of Agriculture, Agronomy building-, 1962-1963 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Agronomy Building Grant. United States Dept, of Health, Education and Welfare; New York State College of Agriculture, Agronomy building., 1962-1963 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Alumni Association. Robinson, Donald G.; New York State College of Agriculture, Alumni Association., 1962-1963 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Cornell University College of Architecture. Kelly, Burnham; Jones, Barclay; SUNY College at Geneseo., 1962 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Argentine Exchange Student. Patrick, George F.; Foulon, Luis A.; Univ. of Buenos Aires., 1962-1963 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Associate Coordinator of Research. Hastie, John W.; Rogers, Thomas R.; Lowe, Jack W.; United States Dept, of Health, Education and Welfare., 1962-1963 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Howard E. Babcock Professorship. Call, David L.; DeGraff, Herrell., 1962-1963 (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - Bakia Club. Cornell University, Pilipino Club., 1963 (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - Board of Trustees. Stamp, Neal R.; Crowe, Cyril F.; Peterson, Arthur H.; Cornell University, Board of Trustees., 1962-1963 (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - Board of Trustees - Presentation: New York Changing and Adjusting Agriculture., 1962-1963 (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - Botany, Applications, Headship. Alston, Ralph E.; Cochrane, Vincent W.; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept, of Botany., 1962-1963 (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - Buildings and Properties. Graeper, William G.; Humphreys, John W., 1962-1963 (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - Calendar of Events., 1962-1963 (Box 13, Folder 39)
  - Conservation, Saranac Lake Property. Swanson, Gustav A.; Webster, Dwight A.; Ross, Donald; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept, of Conservation., 1962-1963 (Box 13, Folder 40)
  - Conservation Workshop., 1962-1963 (Box 13, Folder 41)
  - "Cornell Countryman.", 1962-1963 (Box 13, Folder 42)
  - Credit Union. Cornell Federal Credit Union., 1962 (Box 13, Folder 43)
  - Cornell University Center for International Studies. Mellor, John W.; Muller, Steven., 1962-1963 (Box 13, Folder 44)
  - Cornell University Council., 1962-1963 (Box 13, Folder 45)
  - Cornell University Counsel, Stamp and Meigs. Meigs, Robert B.; Stamp, Neal R.; Cornell University, Office of the Counsel., 1962-1963 (Box 13, Folder 46)
  - Agriculture College Council Meeting 1 NOV 1962. New York State College of Agriculture, Advisory Council., 1962-1963 (Box 13, Folder 47)
  - Agriculture College Council. Adams, Morton; Fallon, Edmund H.; Mitchell, Albert K.; New York State College of Agriculture, Advisory Council., 1962-1963 (Box 13, Folder 48)
  - College Council, Geneva., 1962-1963 (Box 13, Folder 49)
  - Eastman Stage., 1962-1963 (Box 13, Folder 50)
  - Entomology, Applicants. Steinhaus, Edward A.; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept, of Entomology and Limnology., 1962-1963 (Box 13, Folder 51)
  - Equipment Purchasing for New Facilities., 1962-1963 (Box 13, Folder 52)